<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../xslt/fcs_html.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE character SYSTEM "../Mindjammer/character.dtd">
<character>
  <id>
    <charname>Dafny</charname>
    <playername>Jennifer Cornish</playername>
    <description>
      Arboe (Blue, pg 11)
      "Humans with prehensile feet and enhanced balance and jumping ability who live in forests
      and low-gravity environments. Some are furred, but most are not. Some arboes are adapted
      to hold their breath for long periods, and survive up to 30 minutes even in vacuum."
    </description>
    <homeworld name="Fathom" ref="FH 8" habituated-gravity="?" tech-index="7"/>
  </id>
  <aspects>
    <aspect type="High-Concept">Diplomatic Jack-Of-All-Trades</aspect>
    <aspect type="Trouble">Fighting an Uphill Battle</aspect> <!-- mainly prejudice against Canopy -->
    <aspect phase-num="1"></aspect>
    <aspect></aspect>
    <aspect></aspect>
  </aspects>
  <skills>
    <skill rating="4" name="Rapport"/>

    <skill rating="3" name="Bureaucracy"/>
    <skill rating="3" name="Intrusion"/>

    <skill rating="2" name="Athletics"/>
    <skill rating="2" name="Empathy"/>
    <skill rating="2" name=""/>

    <skill rating="1" name=""/>
    <skill rating="1" name=""/>
    <skill rating="1" name=""/>
    <skill rating="1" name=""/>
  </skills>
  <extras>
    <extra>Adaptation: (Forest Canopy or Vacuum or Low-Grav), Cf. MJ pg106</extra>
  </extras>
  <languages>
  </languages>
  <stunts>
    <stunt name="Ready for Contingencies">
      +2 to one roll within a Challenge involving a first-time interaction.
    </stunt>
    <stunt name="I Knit with Red Tape">
      +2 to Overcome with Bureaucracy when dealing with a foreign culture.
    </stunt>
    <stunt name="&#160;">
      &#160;
    </stunt>
  </stunts>
  <consequences>
  </consequences>
  <hacks credit-stress="true"/>
  <phase-trio>
    <phase num="1">
      <events>
        From the Canopy colony on the planet Fathom |
        Canopy's "Chamber of Commerce" paid for her Interplanetary Relations degree, went back home to work for them |
        Met Junior at the University of Kallistan
      </events>
    </phase>
    <phase num="2">
      <events>&#160;</events>
    </phase>
    <phase num="3">
      <events>&#160;</events>
    </phase>
  </phase-trio>
  <notes>
    Canopy
      Canopy is entirely in the upper trees on some large continent with Opteran ruins
      Some other more isolationist settlement is on a different landmass
        They rely on Canopy to deal with outsiders and don't allow visitors
      Fathom has Opteran ruins, the others avoid such ruins due to religious taboo
        (part of why they live on a different landmass)

    Aspects
      "Finders Keepers",
        (material goods should be used where they do the most utilitarian good)
        (adulthood is equated with having the capacity to make such decisions)
    Other potentials
      "We Take Care of Our Own",
      "Live and Let Live",
      "Aspiring to Join the Protectorate",
      "Don't Underestimate Us",
      "Redneck Justice"

    Questions:
      What's the most interesting or important thing to know about you that has nothing to do with your relationship to your homeworld?
    Whatcha doin'?
      Getting needed supplies for the colony world
      Mysteries about Fathom's unexplored areas
      Increasing the social standing of Canopy in the eyes of the Haven Hub
        sponsoring a cultural event
        bringing a scholar to give a lecture or study Fathom
        other
      Dealing with organized crime
      Dealing with internal conflicts within Canopy
      Establishing a new trade relationship (like Quark and the Tulaberry wine)
      The PCs covering the tracks of their own personal secrets
      Getting free trader jobs to pay your own bills (Firefly, etc.)
      Trying to get new immigrants
  </notes>
</character>
