<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../xslt/fcs_html.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE character SYSTEM "character.dtd">
<character>
  <id>
    <charname>Martin Imiritish ke'Tolosa Liú</charname>
    <playername>Kevin C. Baird</playername>
    <description>
    Slightly below-average sized Elf of Han Chinese ancestry (186 cm, 70 Kg). Medium-length black hair.
    Often wears glasses as a Google Glass-style HMD for commlink (as many people do).
    Typically dresses a bit more formally than is standard for Tarislar.
  </description>
  </id>
  <aspects>
    <aspect type="High-Concept">Elven 巫人 Expat in Tarislar</aspect>
    <aspect type="Trouble">Find a Clever Way to Minimize Harm</aspect>
    <aspect phase-num="1">American-Born Chinese</aspect>
    <aspect phase-num="2">Liberal Patriot from PDX</aspect>
    <aspect phase-num="3">Tír Tairngire Border Patrol Lt. (Retired)</aspect>
  </aspects>
  <skills>
    <skill rating="3" name="Will"/>

    <skill rating="2" name="Contacts"/>
    <skill rating="2" name="Lore"/>
    <skill rating="2" name="Persuade"/>

    <skill rating="1" name="Athletics"/>
    <skill rating="1" name="Notice"/>
    <skill rating="1" name="Physique"/>
    <skill rating="1" name="Shoot"/>
  </skills>
  <approaches>
    <approach rating="2" name="Magic"/>
    <approach rating="1" name="Careful"/>
    <approach rating="1" name="Clever"/>
  </approaches>
  <extras>
    <extra>Magician: 巫人 (wū rén) in the 五行 (wŭ xíng) tradition</extra>
    <gadget name="Cultured Bioware">
      <function>Cerebral Booster</function>
      <flaws>
        <flaw>Reduces Essence</flaw>
      </flaws>
    </gadget>
    <gadget name="Talisman">
      <function>Power Focus</function>
      <flaws>
        <flaw>Geas: reduces Magical power when absent</flaw>
        <flaw>Suggests 五行 Tradition</flaw>
      </flaws>
      <aspects>
        <aspect>Ox bone 麻将 (májiăng) tile bracelet</aspect>
      </aspects>
      <benefits>
        <benefit name="Summoning Aid">
          +2 to Create an Advantage with Conjuring when initially summoning a Spirit
        </benefit>
      </benefits>
    </gadget>
  </extras>
  <stunts>
    <stunt name="Quick Summoner">
      Allows Conjuring at will, rather than as a lengthy ritual that requires a summoning circle.
    </stunt>
  </stunts>
  <consequences/>
  <phase-trio>
    <phase num="1" title="Childhood">
      <events>
        2035: Tír Tairngire secedes from SSC; CFS kicked out of UCAS
        2036: TT invades northern CFS to Redding
        2041-2044: Nationalist War in China
        2042: Liu's parents emigrate from Beijing to TT
        2046-05-08 17:15:12 -0700: Liu born in Cara'Sir (Portland), TT
        Both parents are 1st Generation Han Chinese Elves who emigrated from
        greater Beijing to Tír Tairngire, motivated by the welcoming-to-metahumans
        rhetoric of TT's founding and the unrest in China at that time.

        Under Tír Tairngire's autocratic government, Martin was a member of the
        Rinelle ke'Tesrae's moderate/liberal wing, favoring democratic elections
        and a reduction/elimination of the formal caste system. Since the elections
        of 2065, he eschews revolutionary action in favor of "within the system"
        reforms. He has no particular admiration for the previous unelected
        Princes, and adheres to no significant racism directed at either metatypes
        or ethnic backgrounds, thereby opposing the Elf supremacist factions in the
        Rinelle [LOP7-8/SofNA142-3]. His family spoke mainly 普通话 at home. His
        true native language is now Sperethiel, and he has a strong non-native
        command of English.
      </events>
    </phase>
    <phase num="2" title="Early Adulthood">
      <events>
        2064: Liu undergoes Rite of Passage [TT57]. For the Bridging portion, he
        went to Anthony Lakes, Whitman National Forest in Northeastern Tír
        Tairngire. Tír Tairngirenes can be issued their standard Peace Force
        survival knife before deferred military service so they can use it in the
        Bridging, as Liu did. For the Naming portion, he chose to replace his birth
        name Resperentish with Imiritish ke'Tolosa, and made appropriate democratic
        reforms to the usual declarations of loyalty, cf. Reconstructionist Judaic
        bar mitzvah.
        2065: 1st open TT elections, Larry Zincan elected High Prince. Liu voted for him.
        2067: PCC absorbs Ute nation w/much Ute unrest
      </events>
    </phase>
    <phase num="3" title="The Near-Present">
      <events>
        2068: Martin gets B.A. in Applied Thaumaturgy from UTT in Serentaneyo
        (Eugene), starts mandatory 2-year military service in Border Patrol. Liu
        served as a Lt. in the Border Patrol due to his parents being Chivalry rank
        [TT59].
        2070: 2nd open TT elections, Zincan re-elected. Liu votes for him as High
        Prince again. Of the other Princes, he has spoken most approvingly of Jake
        Foster &amp; Amy Joubert [LOP14], with some support as well for Conall
        Taylor [LOP15]. 4th Rite of Progression held, Liu does not participate due
        to extended wilderness/border assignments for his military service, which
        he completes later that year.
    
        2072: M.A. in Applied Thaumaturgy from UTT in Serentaneyo (Eugene); Liu
        moves to Tarislar, Puyallup [Seattle126]. Lives a Low lifestyle near the
        hospital Deireadh an Tuartheil, "The End of the Song of the People/Tribe"
        [Seattle128, SS:HSLL12-13], where he volunteers with Health spells.
      </events>
    </phase>
  </phase-trio>
  <notes>
    For even more detail, we could define the 五行 tradition as a character via the Fate Fractal.
 </notes>
</character>
