<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../xslt/fcs_html.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE character SYSTEM "character.dtd">
<character>
  <id>
    <charname>Nima Shirazi</charname>
    <playername>Kevin Baird</playername>
    <description>
      Originally an Iranian-American computer scientist and roboticist from Orange County, CA.
      After contracting a terminal illness, successfully transferred consciousness into a small
      (5ish) cadre of robotic insectoid bodies. Given the economics of micro-electronics
      manufacturing, he's now mostly Chinese.
    </description>
  </id>
  <aspects>
    <aspect type="High-Concept">Brilliant Transhumanist Visionary</aspect>
    <aspect type="Trouble">Strahd Will Pay</aspect>
    <aspect phase-num="1">Ghostcomp in Multiple Insectoid Cybershells</aspect>
    <aspect phase-num="2">Nima Knows</aspect>
    <aspect></aspect>
  </aspects>
  <skills>
    <!--
    Want
      Lore
      Notice
      Rapport
      X Hacking
      Stealth
      X Will

    Do Not Want
      Contacts
      Drive
      Fight
      Physique
      Shoot

    Not Sure
      Athletics
      Burglary
      Crafts
      Deceive
      Empathy
      Investigate
      Provoke

    -->
    <skill rating="4" name="Hacking"/>

    <skill rating="3" name="&#160;"/>
    <skill rating="3" name="Will"/>

    <skill rating="2" name="&#160;"/>
    <skill rating="2" name="&#160;"/>
    <skill rating="2" name="&#160;"/>

    <skill rating="1" name="&#160;"/>
    <skill rating="1" name="&#160;"/>
    <skill rating="1" name="&#160;"/>
    <skill rating="1" name="&#160;"/>
  </skills>
  <languages>
    Speaks English and Farsi natively. Probably a smattering of Arabic.
    He's probably enough of a douche to want to speak French just because.
  </languages>
  <extras>
    <gadget name="Uruk Systems" cost="1">
      <function>Billion-Dollar Bio- and Info-Tech Company</function>
      <flaws>
        <flaw>Gotta Keep the Public and Shareholders Happy</flaw>
        <flaw>High Profile; Easy to Find</flaw>
      </flaws>
      <aspects>
        <aspect>Intrusion Countermeasures Against Vampires and Other Threats</aspect>
        <aspect>Bringing Tomorrow's Technology to the Public</aspect>
        <aspect>Adnan the Robot Butler</aspect>
        <aspect>Very Smart People Work Here</aspect>
      </aspects>
      <benefits>
        <benefit name="Prototypes ☐ ☐">
          A team of roboticists is constantly tinkering with the features of his robot bodies.
          Twice per session, can declare an Aspect with a free Invocation to represent that. (T:SBS, pg48)
        </benefit>
      </benefits>
    </gadget>
  </extras>
  <stunts>
    <stunt name="Attention to Detail">
      You can use Investigate instead of Empathy to defend against Deceive attempts. What others discover
      through gut reactions and intuition, you learn through careful observation of microexpressions.
    </stunt>
    <stunt name="Body Language Reader">
      You can use Notice in place of Empathy to learn the aspects of a target through observation.
    </stunt>
    <stunt name="Drinks the Kool-Aid">
      May use Rapport instead of Deceive to Overcome when
      he believes he's ultimately doing the right thing.
    </stunt>
    <stunt name="No, YOU Move">
      When you use Will to Defend against fear or intimidation, on a Success With Style
      instead of gaining a Boost you can inflict a 2-shift mental hit on the attacker.
      (M12, pg42)
    </stunt>
    <stunt name="Revenge Is A Dish Best Served By Infomorphs, You Murderous Undead Bloodsucker">
      Gain a +3 bonus instead of +2 when Invoking Strahd Will Pay.
    </stunt>
    <stunt name="Robot Bodies Make No Cortisol">
      Immune to attempts to Create Advantages describing emotional states more extreme than cool, rational ones.
    </stunt>
    <stunt name="Seen It All">
      Armor: 2 vs. mental attacks (M12, pg25)
    </stunt>
    <stunt name="Smartlinks">
      May use Hacking to Attack when invoking Aspects describing computer-controller weapons.
    </stunt>
    <stunt name="Standing On the Shoulders of Van Helsing">
      +2 to Create (recall) an Advantage with Lore directly pertaining to vampirism.
    </stunt>
    <stunt name="Xanatos Speed Chess ☐">
      Once per Session, after failing to Overcome vs. the Big Bad, rename one Situation Aspect already
      in play, representing your ability to shift long-term plans to account for new developments.
    </stunt>
    <!--
    <stunt name="Careful Shot">
      When you take time to aim for an exchange prior to shooting, you may use
      Survival to Attack instead of Shoot. (AA, pg119)
    </stunt>
    -->
  </stunts>
  <consequences/>
  <phase-trio>
    <phase num="1">
      <events>
        Contracted a terminal illness, sailed to international waters for a destructive braintaping
        with Darcy's help. Sometime before that, Strahd vamped his child, who Nima had to kill/put
        down/destroy. The mother is presumed by Nima to have been killed by the child, but he may
        be mistaken.
      </events>
    </phase>
    <phase num="2">
      <events>
        Nima hired a team of lawyers to defend Susan or get her case never to
        come to trial with the understanding that she come work for his team.
      </events>
    </phase>
  </phase-trio>
</character>
