<?xml version = '1.0'?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../xslt/atomic-robo_html.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE atomic-robo SYSTEM "../AtomicRobo/atomic-robo.dtd">
<character>
 <id>
  <charname>Frank Rogers (Special Agent)</charname>
  <playername>Michael Wood</playername>
  <affiliation>Tesladyne SF (Action Scientist PC)</affiliation>
  <description>
    TBD
  </description>
 </id>
 <current-fate-points>3</current-fate-points>
 <experience-points>0</experience-points>
 <aspects>
  <aspect type="Concept">TBD</aspect>
  <aspect type="Mode" mode-name="Telepath">TBD</aspect>
  <aspect type="Mode" mode-name="Martial Artist">TBD</aspect>
  <aspect type="Mode" mode-name="Special Agent">TBD</aspect>
  <aspect type="Omega">The Batman of Human Resources</aspect>
 </aspects>
 <skills>
  <mode rating="3" name="Telepath" stress-type="mental"> <!-- ARRPG pg92 -->
   <skill name="Deceive"/>
   <skill name="Empathy"/>
   <!-- OR Focus 1 Trained Skill instead of Hallucinations -->
   <skill name="Hallucinations"/>
   <skill name="Provoke"/>
   <skill name="Rapport"/>
   <skill name="Will"/>
  </mode>
  <mode rating="2" name="Martial Artist" stress-type="physical"> <!-- ARRPG pg88 -->
   <skill name="Athletics"/>
   <skill name="Combat"/>
   <skill name="Notice"/>
   <skill name="Physique"/>
   <skill name="Stealth"/>
   <skill name="Will"/>
  </mode>
  <mode rating="1" name="Special Agent"> <!-- ARRPG pg276 -->
   <skill name="Contacts"  cost="1"/>
   <skill name="Deceive"   cost="2"/>
   <skill name="Notice"    cost="1"/>
   <skill name="Stealth"   cost="2"/>
   <skill name="Vehicles"  cost="2"/>
   <skill name="Will"      cost="1"/>
  </mode>
 </skills>
 <stunts>
  <stunt name="Biofeedback">
   You are capable of using your psionic powers to enhance your physical
   capabilities for a short time. You must make an Overcome roll to enter the
   proper trance state for this power, and anyone who can reasonably disrupt
   your concentration may oppose you. (Alternately, you may take a Mild
   Consequence to automatically succeed.)
   If you succeed, you may raise Athletics OR Physique by +2 for the remainder
   of the scene, with all the benefits of doing so (which could mean more
   stress boxes and whatnot). If you succeed with style, you may raise BOTH.
   --DAR33
  </stunt>
  <stunt name="Borrowed Knowledge">
   Pick another character (PC or NPC) who's in the scene with you. You can use
   one of their skills for one roll in this scene, whether it's a skill you
   already have or not. When you do this, pay that character a fate point.
  </stunt>
  <stunt name="Iron Robe Technique">
   Armor: 2
  </stunt>
  <stunt name="Lightning Reflexes">
   In a physical conflict, you always act first. If someone else in the
   conflict has a stunt that gives them the same ability, make an Athletics
   roll to see who goes first.
  </stunt>
  <stunt name="Mind Reader">
   When you use Empathy to create an advantage by discovering another
   character's aspects, you don't need to speak with them and it takes
   virtually no time.
  </stunt>
  <stunt name="One With Everything">
   Use Will to create an advantage through meditation or
   focus when you have a moment to breathe and concentrate.
  </stunt>
  <stunt name="Remote Viewing">
   Pick a character you’ve met (PC or NPC), whether or not they’re in the scene
   with you. You can briefly perceive using their senses instead of your own.
   The clarity of your perception will depend on the distance involved and how
   well you know the other character. For example, if you’re seeing through the
   eyes of your brother in the next room, it’ll be crystal clear. If you’re
   seeing through the eyes of a Majestic 12 guard several miles away with whom
   you spoke a few days ago, it’ll be blurry and unreliable.
  </stunt>
  <stunt name="Versatile Will">
   Switch ANY skill with Will once per scene
  </stunt>
 </stunts>
 <consequences>
 </consequences>
 <experiences>
  <experience/>
  <experience/>
  <experience/>
 </experiences>
 <notes/>
</character>
