<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../xslt/fate-freeport_html.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE character SYSTEM "../FateCore/character.dtd">
<character>
  <id>
    <charname>Gadi Melaku 稳 of the Ayhudi clan</charname>
    <playername>Kevin C. Baird</playername>
    <description>
      &#160;
    </description>
  </id>
  <refresh base="6" free-stunts="0"/>
  <aspects>
    <aspect type="High-Concept">Gold Dwarf Wizard from the Great Rift</aspect>
    <aspect type="Trouble">Must Prove Myself Worthy to my Prospective In-Laws</aspect>
    <aspect phase-num="1">Close to Zasheida's Family in Calimport</aspect>
    <aspect phase-num="2">M.M.S. from the Academy Arcane</aspect>
    <aspect phase-num="3">Border Patrol in the Steel Shields</aspect>
  </aspects>
  <skills shape="flat">
    <skill rating="1" name="Strength"/>
    <skill rating="2" name="Dexterity"/>
    <skill rating="2" name="Constitution"/>
    <skill rating="3" name="Intelligence"/>
    <skill rating="1" name="Wisdom"/>
    <skill rating="0" name="Charisma"/>
  </skills>
  <languages>
    Common, Draconic, Dwarvish, Elvish. Still trying to learn Halruaan.
  </languages>
  <extras>
    <gadget cost="1" name="War Wizard">
      <function>
        2 Abjuration or Evocation spells. Uses Intellignce instead of Charisma for casting.
      </function>
      <benefits>
        <benefit cost="0" name="Arcane Shield">
          (Abjuration, Cost, Persistent): Add your Intelligence to your Dexterity when
          defending against attacks that cause physical stress.
          FFC pg33
        </benefit>
        <benefit cost="0" name="Magic Missile">
          (Evocation): Launch a bolt of pure arcane energy at a single target in your current
          or an adjacent zone. You must be able to see the target. Attack action, caster’s Charisma
          vs. target’s Dexterity, attack does physical stress.
          FFC pg38
        </benefit>
      </benefits>
    </gadget>
    <gadget cost="1" name="Manipulator">
      <function>
        3 Transmutation spells.
      </function>
      <benefits>
        <benefit cost="0" name="Alter Surface">
          (Transmutation, Cost, Persistent): You change the surface of a solid object in your
          zone (such as the ground, a sword handle, etc.), applying a new aspect that you or your
          allies gain two free invocations on. Choose one of the following: Slippery Footing, Razor
          Sharp Corners, Weakened By Dry Rot, or invent your own. You can’t apply this to
          objects being worn by an unwilling creature (such as armor).
          FFC pg42
        </benefit>
        <benefit cost="0" name="Grace">
          (Transmutation, Prayer, Cost, Persistent): You or a willing ally in your zone gains +1 to
          Dexterity. Multiple castings of Grace on the same target in the same scene do not stack.
          FFC pg42
        </benefit>
        <benefit cost="0" name="Knock">
          (Transmutation, Trickster, Cost): You can attempt to open a lock. The overcome roll is your
          Charisma +2 vs. the standard difficulty to pick the lock, or the caster’s charisma +2 roll if
          it’s magically sealed (see spell “Seal” below).
          FFC pg42
        </benefit>
      </benefits>
    </gadget>
    <gadget cost="1" name="Seer">
      <function>
        3 divination spells.
      </function>
      <benefits>
        <benefit cost="0" name="Detect Magic">
          (Divination, Trickster): When you cast Detect Magic, you become aware of all
          magically-generated situation aspects in your zone.
          FFC pg35
        </benefit>
        <benefit cost="0" name="Fortune">
          (Divination, Cost, Per Session): You may perform a prediction ritual (describe yours -
          runecasting, reading tea leaves, crystal gazing, divination cards, etc.) You glean some insight
          into the future represented by three boosts you or allies may spend; these boosts persist
          until they are spent, or you cast this spell again. This spell requires several minutes to cast,
          usually an entire scene, rather than just one action.
          FFC pg35
        </benefit>
        <benefit cost="0" name="Locate Object">
          (Divination, Trickster, Cost, Persistent, Requires Detect Magic or Detect Impurity):
          This spell allows you to sense the direction to a well-known object. It can be general (find
          the nearest fresh water) or specific (find the treasure map those thieves stole from me).
          FFC pg35
        </benefit>
      </benefits>
    </gadget>
  </extras>
  <stunts>
    <stunt name="Dwarven Toughness">
      You gain an extra mild consequence slot, and you gain a +2 to Constitution-based rolls to resist
      the effects of poison.
    </stunt>
  </stunts>
  <consequences/>
  <hacks corruption="true"/>
  <phase-trio>
    <phase num="1">
      <events>
        &#160;
      </events>
    </phase>
    <phase num="2">
      <events>
        &#160;
      </events>
    </phase>
    <phase num="3">
      <events>
        &#160;
      </events>
    </phase>
  </phase-trio>
  <notes>
    &#160;
  </notes>
</character>
